Guide to the Dept. of Music Records, 1922-Ongoing UA.25.28.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List 1922-Ongoing
  - Graduation, 2014 (Box 28)
  - Opera Workshop, 2014 (Box 28)
  - DUMIC (Rare Music), 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Student Chamber Music, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Duke Chorale, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Djembe + Afro Cuban Ensemble, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - (DNM) Duke New Music Ensemble, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Guest Recitals, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Master Classes, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Family Weekend, 2013 (Box 28)
  - Duke Jazz Ensemble, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Duke University String School (DUSS), 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Baldwin Auditorium Gala Re-opening, 2013 (Box 28)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Student Recitals, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Organ Recitals, FIMTE Concerts, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Event Calendars, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - Publicity materials, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Cd UA25280002-OP-0001)
  - Additional photos and videos, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Cd UA25280002-OP-0002)
- Accession UA2016-0022, 2014-2015; 2
  - Graduation, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Student Chamber Music, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Duke New Music Ensemble (dnme), 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Opera Workshop, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Guest Recitals, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Duke Chorale, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Encounters, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Family Weekend Concerts, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Master Class Series, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Lecture Series, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Duke University String School, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - DUMIC - Rare Music, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Wind Symphony, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Student Recitals, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Music Events Calendars, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Auditions, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Advertising, 2014-2015 (Box 29)
  - Music Department, 2014-2015 (Box 29, Dvd UA25280002-OP-0003)
- Accession UA2017-0029, 2015-2016
  - Event Posters, 2015-2016 (Oversize-folder 6)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Duke Chorale, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Student Chamber Music, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Family Weekend, 2015 (Box 30)
  - Duke String School, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Graduation, 2016 (Box 30)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Guest Recitals, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Graduate Composers and Duke New Music Ensemble (dnme), 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Opera Workshop, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - DUMIC: Rare Music Concert Series, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Jazz, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Student Recitals, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Master Classes, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Lectures, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Calendars, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Music Department Advertising and Brochues, 2015-2016 (Box 30)
  - Music Department, 2015-2016 (Box 30, Optical-disc UA25280002-OP-0004)